Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 35mm Microfilm Proofs, 1906-1960 and undated
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
J. Walter Thompson Company. 35mm Microfilm Proofs 1906-1960 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University
J. Walter Thompson Company.
3.0 Linear Feet 104 Items
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States.
The JWT 35mm Microfilm Proofs collection spans the years 1906-1960 and consists primarily of images of print advertisements and proofs taken from proof books and portfolios of domestic and foreign JWT offices. Clients include Ballantine's, B.F. Goodrich, Butterick, Corning, Crowell Publishing, Davey Tree Surgeons, General Cigar, General Motors, Guinness, Horlicks, J.B. Williams, Jergens, Johns-Manville, Nash, Northam Warren, Pennsylvania RR, RCA, Sharp & Dohme, Shell, Standard Brands, Sun Maid, Swift, Sylvania, United Airlines, Ward Baking, and Welch's Grape Juice. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. 35mm Microfilm Proofs were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1987.
Historical Note
Beginning in the late 1930s, proof books containing advertisements of former clients, foreign clients and domestic clients from offices other than New York were put on microfilm. It is believed that after items were microfilmed, the originals were destroyed.
Collection Overview
The JWT 35mm Microfilm Proofs collection spans the years 1906-1960 and consists primarily of images of print advertisements and proofs taken from proof books and portfolios of domestic and foreign JWT offices. Clients include Ballantine's, B.F. Goodrich, Butterick, Corning, Crowell Publishing, Davey Tree Surgeons, General Cigar, General Motors, Guinness, Horlicks, J.B. Williams, Jergens, Johns-Manville, Nash, Northam Warren, Pennsylvania RR, RCA, Sharp & Dohme, Shell, Standard Brands, Sun Maid, Swift, Sylvania, United Airlines, Ward Baking, and Welch's Grape Juice.
Collection Arrangement
Arranged by reel number and physical sequence of images on microfilm. Items were microfilmed in several categories: general accounts, foreign office clients, western offices, and portfolios of inactive client accounts.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
J. Walter Thompson Company
Andrew Jergens Company (Cincinnati, Ohio)
B.F. Goodrich Company
Butterick Publishing
Corning Glass Works
Crowell Publishing Company
Davey Tree Expert Company (Kent, Ohio)
General Cigar Company (Philadelphia, Pa.)
General Motors Corporation
Guinness (Firm)
J.B. Williams Co
Johns-Manville Corporation
Nash Motors Company
Northam Warren Corporation
P. Ballantine & Sons
Pennsylvania Railroad
Radio Corporation of America
Sharp & Dohme
Shell Oil Company
Standard Brands Incorporated
Sun Maid Growers of California
Swift & Company
Sylvania Electric Products, Inc
United Airlines
Ward Baking Company
Welch Grape Juice Company
Advertising
Advertising -- United States
Advertising -- United States -- History
Advertising agencies
Advertising agencies -- United States
Advertising agencies -- United States -- History
Proofs
Microfilms
John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
Related Material
J. Walter Thompson Company. Account Files
J. Walter Thompson Company. Domestic Advertisements Collection
J. Walter Thompson Company. International Advertisements Collection
J. Walter Thompson Company. International Offices Records
Roy Lightner Collection of Antique Advertisements
Description of Collection
- Accounts, 1906-1941 and undated
  - Addressograph, 1914 (Reel 1)
  - American Appraisal Co. (factory appraisal financial service), 1922
  - American Correspondence School of Law, 1915
  - Arbuckle Brothers (Ariosa, Yuban coffees), 1913-1924
  - Elizabeth Arden, 1923
  - Artloom (rugs), 1937
  - Associated Tile Manufacturers (Keromic tiles), 1928
  - Automatic Electric Co. (interoffice telephones), 1915-1917
  - Audit Bureau of Circulations, 1930-1933
  - Ballard (Oven-ready biscuits), 1931-1933
  - Ballard (Oven-ready biscuits), 1931-1933 (continued) (Reel 2)
  - A.B.A. Cheques, 1915
  - Belding Brothers & Co. (silks, fabric), 1908-1910
  - Barbours Linen Thread, 1924-1927
  - A. Bellor & Co. (ladies' cloaks, suits, dresses), 1920-1927
  - Berkey & Gay (furniture), 1917-1919
  - Canadian Colonial Airways, 1929-1931
  - Bartlett Pears, 1937
  - Bishopric Manufacturing Co. (building materials), 1925-1927
  - Bischof (ladies' clothing), 1914-1915
  - Paul Block (pictorial revue), 1917-1929
  - Bocaire (Turner and Walls men's shirts and shirting), 1921-1922
  - Paul Von Boeckman (physical culture), 1914
  - Boeing School of Aeronautics, 1937-1938
  - Bontex (H.B. Oaflin Co.; wash fabrics and dresses), undated
  - Borax Soap Chips, 1917-1918
  - A.S. Boyle (Old English Floor Wax), 1917-1922
  - Brenlin Window Shades (Chaow Breneman Co.), 1915-1926
  - Brunswick-Balke-Collender (bowling equipment), 1940
  - Burry Biscuit co., 1937-1939
  - Butterick, 1922-1925
  - Butterick, 1922-1925 (continued) (Reel 3)
  - Carter's Underwear, 1913-1932
  - Edward A. Cassidy (Kimbal Auto Jacks, Casco Tire Pump, C. Piel Co., G.P. Muffler Cut-out), 1917-1920
  - CECO (radio tubes), 1930
  - Central Bank of Oakland, 1934-1935
  - Central Public Service Corp. (utility), 1930-1933
  - Chatham Manufacturing Co. (blankets, sheets, pillowcases), 1925-1940
  - Chicago, Burlington & Quincy R.R., 1925-1931
  - Chicago, Burlington & Quincy R.R., 1925-1931 (continued) (Reel 4)
  - Close's Pocket Candies (George Close Co.), 1920
  - Coast Fishing Co. (Balto dog food, Puss and Boots cat food), 1933-1936
  - Cofield Motor Washer (washing machines), 1914
  - Colgate & Co. (toilet goods), 1906-1914
  - Cortley Clothes (Cohen Cohn and Lang; men's clothes), 1921
  - C.E. Conover Co. (Naiad dress shields), 1906-1917
  - Cooper's (men's underwear), 1939
  - Continental Motor Manufacturing Co., 1914-1920
  - Corning Glass Works (baby bottles, kitchen utensils, laboratory equipment, Steuben glass, Conaphore, auto headlight lenses), 1918-
  - Corning Glass Works (baby bottles, kitchen utensils, laboratory equipment, Steuben glass, Conaphore, auto headlight lenses), 1918- (continued) (Reel 5)
  - Corticelli Silk Co. (dresses, hosiery, silk thread, knitting yarns), 1924-1928
  - Cox Confectionary Co. (Romance chocolates), 1920-1925
  - Cream of Wheat, 1923-1938
  - Columbia Broadcasting System (CBS, WBBM radio station), undated
  - Crosley Radio, 1929
  - Crowell Publishing Company (American, Collier's, Farm and Fireside, Woman's Home Companion magazines), 1924-1927
  - Crowell Publishing Company (American, Collier's, Farm and Fireside, Woman's Home Companion magazines), 1924-1927 (continued) (Reel 6)
  - Atlantic Coast Fisheries Inc. (Chesebro Bros & Robbins, Inc. fish brokers, Nordic frozen fish steaks), 1929-1931
  - Alkalithia Co. (drugs), 1938-1939
  - Curtiss Candy Co. (Baby Ruth chewing gum and candy bar, Chico peanuts), 1928-1931
  - Curtis Publishing Co. (Ladies Home Journal), 1931-1938
  - Curtis Wood Work, 1913
  - City Baking Co. (Mrs. Schmidt's bread), 1926
  - Curtis Flying Service, undated
  - Davey Tree Surgeons, 1911-1937
  - Davey Tree Surgeons, 1911-1937 (continued) (Reel 7)
  - Curtis Wright Trade, 1929
  - Davey Tree Surgeons, 1911-1937
  - Del Ray Foods (spaghetti), 1933
  - Derryvale Givens (linens), 1917
  - Detroit Brewing Co., 1937
  - Diamond Crystal Salt, 1922-1925
  - Dictaphone, 1916
  - Doubleday Page Co. (book publishers), 1914
  - Douglas Lighter (Hargraft & Co., cigarette lighters), 1926
  - Driecer & Co., 1926
  - Drakes Cakes, 1911-1916
  - Durham Duplex Razor Co., 1934-1938
  - Dwight Anchor (sheets and pillowcases), undated
  - Easy Washing Machines, 1938-1939
  - Eberhard Pencil Co. (Faber, Mongol pencils, Van Dyck and Kleerit erasers), 1929-1936
  - Electric Boat Co. (Nelsco diesel engines, New London Ship and Engine Co., Elco cruisers), 1925-1932
  - Elms and Sellon (D&J Anderson Ginghams fabrics, Standish fabrics), 1923-1926
  - Elms and Sellon (D&J Anderson Ginghams fabrics, Standish fabrics), 1923-1926 (continued) (Reel 8)
  - Emerson Drug So. (Bromo-Seltzer), 1935-1940
  - Erskine & Danforth (Danersk furniture), 1920-1927
  - Felt & Tarront Manufacturing Co. (Comptometer), 1931
  - Exchange Trust Co. (banking), 1908-1916, 1925-1927
  - Felt & Tarront Manufacturing Co. (Comptometer), 1931
  - Fidelio Brewery, 1933-1934
  - Fiske & Co. (Frisklock, Tapestry bricks), 1914-1917
  - Flintkote Corp. (building materials), 1934
  - Foamite-Childs Corp. (fire protection, fire foam), 1923-1927
  - Foamite-Childs Corp. (fire protection, firefoam), 1923-1927 (continued) (Reel 9)
  - Foremost Dairy Products Inc. (Foremost ice cream and milk), 1929-1931
  - Augusta Ice and Coal Co. (Allburn coal), 1929
  - Wm. Freihofer Baking Co. (bread), 1929-
  - Robert Gair & Co., Inc. (package merchandising), 1920-1924
  - Robert Gair & Co., Inc. (Harmony, Garner fabrics), 1927-1928
  - Gates Tours (vacation cruises), 1921-1926
  - P.A. Geier Co. (Royal electric vacuum cleaner), 1921-1924
  - General Shoe Co. (Jorman, Fortune shoes), 1938
  - General Timber Service Inc. (Weyerhauser Forest Products, Balsane wool blankets, insulation division), 1926-1933 (Reel 10)
  - Gill Bros. (lighting fixtures), 1914-1915
  - Globe-Wernicke (office equipment), 1927
  - Good Luck Food Co. (Good Luck for Lemon pie filling), 1922-1926
  - B.F. Goodrich (rubber products; Zippers overshoes, rubber footwear and soles/heels, airplane tires, Goodrich Silvertown, Brunswick, Diamond, Cavalier, Miller, Hood automobile tires, Farren-oid fan belts, mechanical and drug sundries, Miller Rubber Products toys and etc., Celeste spray douche, Sojourn fountain syringe, Diamond rubber belts, marine equipment), 1928-1933
  - B.F. Goodrich (rubber products; Zippers overshoes, rubber footwear and soles/heels, airplane tires, Goodrich Silvertown, Brunswick, Diamond, Cavalier, Miller, Hood automobile tires, Farren-oid fan belts, mechanical and drug sundries, Miller Rubber Products toys and etc., Celeste spray douche, Sojourn fountain syringe, Diamond rubber belts, marine equipment), 1928-1933 (continued) (Reel 11)
  - Graham (Graham Bradley tractor, automobiles), 1937-1939
  - Grand Trunk Railway Line, 1920
  - Griedesieck Western Brewery (Stag, Oldbrau beer), 1937-1940
  - Gruen Watchmakers Guild (Verithin watch), 1915-1932 (Reel 12)
  - Gulbransen (player pianos), 1926
  - Hammond Organ, 1936
  - Hanovia Chemical Manufacturers (Alpine sun lamp, Kromayer lamp), 1928-1930
  - Hall-Borchet Dress Form Co., undated
  - Hasslers Manufacturing Co. (auto shock absorbers), 1927-1928
  - Hathaway Baking Co. (Dolly Madison, Dietz bread, Hathaway's bread), 1926-1934
  - Richard Hellmann Inc. (Hellmann's Blue Ribbon Mayonnaise), 1928
  - Hartsborn Shade Rollers, 1915
  - Peter Henderson (seeds), 1915-1926
  - Henriette (compacts and cigarette cases), 1937-1938
  - Histon Products Co. (drugs, Anatone, Jeltone), undated
  - Wm. Hollins Co. Inc. (Viyella knitting yarns), 1932
  - H.P. Hood & Sons (milk), 1933
  - Hoosier Manufacturing Co. (kitchen cabinets), 1923-1927
  - Hooven-Allison Co. (Bue Heart rope), 1920-1927
  - Horlick's Malted Milk, 1917-1929
  - Horlick's Malted Milk, 1917-1929 (continued) (Reel 13)
  - Howlett & Hockmeyer (Waterside Corduroy suede-like ladies hats, Zip On Body clothes), 1923-1929
  - Richard Hudnut (cosmetics), 1929
  - Deauville & DuBarry (cosmetics), undated
  - Chicago Herald & Examiner, 1928-1929
  - George P. Ide & Co. (shirts and collars), 1926-1927
  - Ideal power lawn mower, 1915
  - Industrial Alcohol Institute (denatured alcohol, antifreeze), 1929
  - Thomas P. Jeffrey Co. (automobiles), 1915
  - Japan Tea Promotion Committee, 1927
  - Jovan Corp. (importers of ginger ale), 1928
  - International Vitamin Corp. (IVC Pearls vitamin capsules), 1930
  - International Silver Co. (premium give-away), 1939
  - International Shoe Corp., undated
  - Andrew Jergens Co. (Woodbury's soap, shaving stick, Jergens Violet Glycerine soap, lotion, Castolay Baby's Soap, Ben Hur perfume), 1911-1936
  - Andrew Jergens Co. (Woodbury's soap, shaving stick, Jergens Violet Glycerine soap, lotion, Castolay Baby's Soap, Ben Hur perfume), 1911-1936 (continued) (Reel 14)
  - A.C. Krum & Sons (macaroni), 1926-1928 (Reel 15)
  - Kops Brothers (Nemo-Flex wonderlift, Sensation Steps, Rapid Medial Belt Co. medical trusses, corsets, brassieres), 1925-1934
  - Klein Rapid Shoe Repair Co., 1929
  - Klear Flox Linen Rug Co., 1922
  - A&M Karaghensian (Herati rugs), 1924-1927
  - Johnson & Johnson (Johnson's baby powder), 1925
  - Jobbers's Overall Co. (Blue Buckle overalls, work clothes), 1920
  - La Gerardine Inc. (La Gerardine hair set, Gray Ban hair rinse, Insto-Wave hair set), 1930-1933
  - Lamont Corliss & Co. (Peppermint Loriots candy), 1920
  - Langendorf United Bakeries (California Spun Slices, Pro Perland's Wheat Bread, Old Homestead bread, Royalets cupcakes), 1922-
  - Langendorf United Bakeries (California Spun Slices, Pro Perland's Wheat Bread, Old Homestead bread, Royalets cupcakes), 1922- (continued) (Reel 16)
  - Lansdowne (Schweiger, Inc., embroidery patterns, dresses), 1914-1930
  - Lehn & Fink (Pebeco toothpaste, Bovril beef drink, Fly-Flu exterminators), 1923-1929
  - Leslie Salt, 1934-1936
  - Lever Bros. (Lifebuoy soap, Rinso detergent), 1918-1925
  - J.B. Lippencott Co. (book publishers), 1911-1916 (Reel 17)
  - Lewis Manufacturing Co. (contractors, homes), 1916-1917
  - Log Cabin (syrup), 1922-1925
  - Lyon & Healy (musical instruments), 1919-1920
  - Majestic Co. (coal chutes), 1917
  - W.H. & A.E. Margerison & co. (Martex towels), 1927
  - Matson Navigation Co. (Matson Line cruises), 1929-1931
  - McCall Corp. (McCall's, Red Book magazines), 1932
  - McCawley & Co. (Slip-On children's clothing), 1924-1925
  - Melville Shoe Corp. (Rival, John Ward, Thom McAn men's shoes), 1925
  - Massachusetts Baking Co. (White Rose bread), 1922
  - Mennen Co. (shaving supplies), 1914-1915
  - Meredith Publishing Co. (Successful Living, Better Homes & Gardens magazines), 1928
  - Moorman Manufacturing Co. (feeds), 1928
  - Moorman Manufacturing Co. (feeds), 1928 (continued) (Reel 18)
  - Motor Improvements, Inc. (Purolator oil filters), 1926
  - Old Witch Co. (cleaning ammonia), 1929-1930
  - Olds Motor Works (Oldsmobile), 1914
  - Old Dominion Garment Co. (Blue Buckle overalls), undated
  - Norwich Pharmacal Co. (Unguentine, Vagiforms, Swan shaving cream), 1924
  - Mountain Valley mineral water, 1940
  - National Lumber Promotion Comm. (Nato Lumbers Manufacturing Association co-op), 1928-1932
  - National Electric Cookery Council (promotion), 1932
  - Vanadium Corporation of America (alloys), 1940
  - National Bureau of Surety and Casualty Underwriters (Safe Drivers Reward Plan, casualty insurance), 1938-1939
  - New England Candy Co. (Necco wafers, Balsters & OK), 1927-1929
  - New Jersey Brewers' Association (promotion), 1938
  - New York Chapter of National Music Appreciation Committee, 1940
  - New York Post, 1940
  - Norfolk & Portsmouth (resort), 1924-1928
  - Northern Pacific Railway, 1926-1930
  - Northwestern Expanded Metal Co., 1914
  - Nash Motors Co. (Nash, Lafayette automobiles), 1934
  - Nash Motors Co. (Nash, Lafayette automobiles), 1934 (continued) (Reel 19)
  - Omar Baking Co. (bread and flour), 1937-1938
  - Orange Crush (soft drink), 1934
  - Osgood Deflection Lens (auto headlight lens), 1916
  - O'Sullivan Rubber Co. (rubber shoe heels), 1912-1933
  - Pacific Coast Electric Bureau (promotion), 1934
  - Peace Dale Mills (J.P. Stevens Co., knitting yarns), 1920-1922
  - Palisade Manufacturing Co. (Kitchen Bouquet food flavoring), 1914
  - Parfumerie St. Denis (bath luxuries), 1929
  - J. Parker Pray Inc. (Opalene nail enamel), 1926
  - Parker-Regan Corp. (Betty Bright floor mops), 1927-1929
  - Park-Lexington Corp (Grand Central Palace exhibition hall), undated
  - Pathescope Corp. (industrial films), 1930-1934
  - Pin Ap'A (Lamont Corliss soft drink), 1916
  - J.C. Penney, 1928-1929
  - J.C. Penney, 1928-1929 (continued) (Reel 20)
  - Pineapple Producers Cooperative Association (promotion), 1933
  - Pennsylvania Railroad (passenger travel, freight,, TAT Maddux Airlines, Long Island Railroad, institutional advertising), 1926-1929
  - Pennsylvania Railroad (passenger travel, freight,, TAT Maddux Airlines, Long Island Railroad, institutional advertising), 1926-1929 (continued) (Reel 21)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad (passenger travel, freight,, TAT Maddux Airlines, Long Island Railroad, institutional advertising), 1926-1929 (continued) (Reel 22)
  - Pennsylvania Railroad (passenger travel, freight,, TAT Maddux Airlines, Long Island Railroad, institutional advertising), 1926-1929 (continued) (Reel 23)
  - Pennsylvania Rubber Co. (tires, golf balls, tennis balls, etc.), 1928
  - Permutit Co. (water softener), 1930-1931
  - Peter Kailler Kohler (Lamont Corliss, Peter's chocolate and cocoa, Redges, Nestle), 1919
  - Peter Kailler Kohler (Lamont Corliss, Peter's chocolate and cocoa, Redges, Nestle), 1919 (continued) (Reel 24)
  - Phoenix Hosiery (men's and women's), 1932-1934
  - E.A. Pierce & Co. (The Lansdowne Co.), 1930
  - Permutit Co. (water softener), 1932-1933
  - Piggly Wiggly Stores, 1927
  - Ed. Pinand (Eau de Quinine, Lilac Vegetal, toiletries_, 1926-1929
  - Pope Manufacturing Co. (motorcycles), 1914
  - Franklin Baker Co. Inc. (coconut), 1925-1929
  - Cheek Neal Coffee Co. (Maxwell House), 1925-
  - Cheek Neal Coffee Co. (Maxwell House), 1925- (continued) (Reel 25)
  - Douglas Pectin Corp. (Certo), 1928
  - Postum Cereal Co. (Grape-Nuts), 1924
  - President Suspenders, 1924-1929
  - Florida Citrus Exchange (Florigold oranges), 1937
  - Rowntree & Co. (Chu-Fru candies), 1925
  - Roosevelt Hotel, 1938
  - Roma Wine Co. (Roma, La Boheme wines), 1935
  - Richardson Co. (roofing), 1923
  - Republic Rubber Co. (tires), 1915
  - Reo Truck Co., 1914
  - Reliance Property Management (Ritz-Carlton Atlantic City), 1932
  - Red Cross Shoes (ladies' shoes), 1912-1922
  - Reckitts Ltd. (bath perfume), 1930
  - Realsilk (men's and women's hose), 1931
  - Rayon Institute of America, Inc. (rayon promotion), 1929-1930
  - Red Head spark plug, 1918
  - Rand McNally & Co. (maps, Child Life magazine), 1925
  - Rand McNally & Co. (maps, Child Life magazine), 1925 (continued) (Reel 26)
  - Quaker Oats Co. (Quaker Oats cereal, Aunt Jemima, Muffets cereal, macaroni), 1924-1936
  - Gorham Co. (hotel, household, ecclesiastical silverware, Spaulding Gorham, Black-Starr, Frost Gorham), 1929-1932
  - Standard Brands, Inc. (Fleischmann's Yeast), 1920-1922
  - Standard Brands, Inc. (Fleischmann's Yeast), 1922-1929 (continued) (Reel 27)
  - Standard Brands, Inc. (Fleischmann's Yeast), 1929-1933 (continued) (Reel 28)
  - Standard Brands, Inc. (Fleischmann's Yeast; Life Begins at Forty 1937: see also reel 50), 1933-1938 (continued) (Reel 29)
  - Standard Brands, Inc. (Fleischmann's Yeast; Life Begins at Forty 1937: see also reel 50), 1933-1938 (continued) (Reel 30)
  - Standard Brands, Inc. (Royal Baking Powder), 1923-1932
  - Standard Brands, Inc. (Royal Baking Powder, Gelatin, pudding), 1925-1938 (continued) (Reel 31)
  - Standard Brands, Inc. (Royal Baking Powder, Gelatin, pudding, desserts, mayonnaise, Fleischmann's Gin), 1934-1940 (continued) (Reel 32)
  - Sardine Fisheries of Maine (Maine sardines), 1930
  - Savage Arms Corporation (Savage Stevens guns), 1923
  - Savage Washer & Dryer (washing machines), 1923
  - F. Schumacher & Co. (fabrics), 1922-1929
  - F. Schumacher & Co. (fabrics), 1929-1930 (continued) (Reel 33)
  - Seaboard Rice Milling Co. (Comet rice), 1917
  - Shults Bread Co., 1922-1923
  - Sealcones Inc. (containers), 1931
  - Seamless Rubber Co. (Surgeon's gloves, sporting goods, 1934-1940
  - Lewis Searing Co. (grease cups and cartridges), 1920
  - Seeck & Kade (Persussin, Actin), 1931-1941
  - Senrico Toothpaste Co., 1919
  - Silk Association of America (promotion), 1916-1921
  - R.F. Simmons Co. (chains), 1913-1920
  - Simmons Co. (beds and mattresses), 1927-1928
  - Simmons Co. (beds and mattresses), 1927-1928 (Reel 34)
  - L.C. Smith and Corona Typewriters, Inc., 1930-1932
  - Simmons Co. (mattresses, coil springs, metal beds, studio couches, Beautyrest mattresses), 1932-1938
  - Smokador Manufacturing Co. Inc. (smoke stands), 1928-1929
  - Sonotone Corp. (hearing aids), 1930-1931
  - Sonotone Corp. (hearing aids), 1930-1931 (continued) (Reel 35)
  - Spaulding & Merrick (tobacco), undated
  - Stanley Insulating Co. (vacuum bottles), 1918-1928
  - Sterling Varnish Co. (Nitrex automotive tire coating), 1920
  - Sonora Phonograph Co. (phonograph, radio speakers), 1924-1926
  - Stork Co. (baby pants, sheeting), 1914-1916
  - S.W. Straus & Co. (banking), 1925-1932
  - Sun Maid Raisin Growers, 1923-1925
  - Sun Maid Raisin Growers, 1925-1929 (continued) (Reel 36)
  - Superior Underwear Co., 1914-1919
  - Stewart Phonograph Co., 1921
  - Union Tobacco Co. (Herbert Tareyton cigarettes), 1928-1929
  - Tea Garden Products Co. (preserves, jellies), 1934-1935
  - Tested Products Laboratories Inc. (Placidon stomach relief), 1934
  - Tex-a-kan Flour Mills Co., 1936-1937
  - Tydol (gasoline), 1917-1919
  - Time, Fortune (magazines), 1929-1933
  - Toledo Scale Co., 1929
  - Thermoid Rubber Co. (Hardy universal joints, industrial machinery accessories, tires), 1919-1921
  - Thermoid Rubber Co. (Hardy universal joints, industrial machinery accessories, tires), 1916-1923 (continued) (Reel 37)
  - Town House Hotel, 1936-1937
  - Tromite Corporation (water softener), 1923-1924
  - Trussed Concrete Steel Co. (building materials), 1914-1917
  - International Telephone & Telegraph (postal telegraph, commercial cables), 1929-1931
  - United Airlines (Air Express Division, passenger flights), 1933-1937
  - United Airlines (Air Express Division, passenger flights), 1937-1939 (continued) (Reel 38)
  - United Artists (Hal Roach Studios, Captain Fury), 1939
  - United States Rubber Co. (rubber footwear, Raynsters raincoats, Keds sneakers, Naugahyde traveling bags), 1919-1928
  - U.S. Industrial Alcohol Co. (Pyro antifreeze, Alcorub rubbing alcohol), 1925-1933 (Reel 39)
  - Urbana Wine Co. (Gold Seal champagne and wines), 1934
  - Vauv Co. (publications), 1924-1927
  - Vogue (publication), 1914
  - P.F. Volland Co. (publishers), 1914
  - S. Sternau (Sterno canned heat, Erno nose spray, Spry rubbing compound), 1929-1938
  - Davison Chemical Corp. (Sylox baby powder), 1939
  - Wadsworth Watch Case Co., 1921-1929
  - Wadsworth Watch Case (Henrietta cases), 1937-1938
  - John Wanamaker (department store), 1914
  - Washington State Progress Commission (promotion), 1938
  - W.R. Warner Co. (Sloan's linament, Formamint, Agarol, Stacomb), 1923-
  - Mrs. Emily Watson, Inc. (pie crust), 1924-1927
  - Welch Grape Juice Co. (Grapelade), 1925-1928
  - Welch Grape Juice Co. (Grapelade), 1925-1928 (continued) (Reel 40)
  - Wheeler-Osgood Co. (Laminex doors), 1929-1931